Unleash your powers.
PAW Patrol: The Mighty Movie is a family, comedy,
adventure film directed by Cal Brunker.
A magical meteor crash lands in Adventure City and gives the PAW Patrol
pups superpowers, transforming them into The Mighty Pups.
Skye (voice), played by Mckenna Grace.
Victoria Vance (voice), played by Taraji P. Henson.
Liberty (voice), played by Marsai Martin.
Chase (voice), played by Iain Armitage.
Mayor Humdinger / Cap'n Turbot (voice), played by Ron Pardo.
Sam Stinger (voice), played by Lil Rel Howery.
Paw Patrol: The Mighty Movie is a 2023 Canadian animated action-adventure
comedy film  based on the television series Paw Patrol.
The sequel to Paw Patrol: The Movie (2021), it was directed by Cal
Brunker, who co-wrote the screenplay with Bob Barlen.
The film features an ensemble voice cast, including Mckenna Grace, Taraji P.
Henson, Marsai Martin, Christian Convery, Lil Rel Howery, Kim Kardashian, Chris Rock, Serena Williams, Alan
Kim, Brice Gonzalez, North West, Saint West, James Marsden, Kristen Bell, and Finn Lee-Epp.
In the film, the Paw Patrol pups gain superpowers from crystals inside a meteor and must stop Mayor
Humdinger and his new accomplice Victoria Vance from wreaking havoc in Adventure City.
In August 2021, following the success of the first film, director
Brunker expressed interest in returning for a sequel.
The sequel was greenlit by Spin Master Entertainment in November 2021, with a planned October
13, 2023 release date, before being pushed forward to a September 2023 release.
The film features elements from the Mighty Pups sub-theme of the main show.
Mikros Image in Montreal returned to provide computer-animation,
while the musical score was composed by Pinar Toprak.
Most of the main voice cast was announced in January 2023,
following Henson's casting in May 2022.
Paw Patrol: The Mighty Movie was released in Canada by Elevation Pictures and in the United States by Paramount Pictures on September 29, 2023, it
received mixed reviews from critics and was a financial success, grossing $205 million against a production budget of $30 million.
A third film, Paw Patrol: The Dino Movie, is in development.
The film explores themes of superhero, cartoon, mad scientist, sequel, dog.
The tone is lighthearted.